palmyrabowl.com 2013-06-06

# Palmyra Bowling | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Any information gathered will be used by Palmyra Bowling. Palmyra Bowling recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of our Internet properties. We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users' right to privacy and to guide our relationships with our users. This Privacy Policy is subject to change at Palmyra Bowling's sole discretion. You should check back every time you visit the site to review the current policy.

### Information Collected

Palmyra Bowling collects information about users during their registration, their inquiries, their participation in certain activities on our website, including contests and polls, and through the use of cookies. When users request pages from our server, our web server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. These addresses are used by computers on the network to send the requested pages to users. 

### Use of Information

Palmyra Bowling will not sell or distribute user information to outside third parties. Except as may be required by law or court order, Palmyra Bowling will not reveal to any third party any personal information that users provide to Palmyra Bowling without the permission of the users. Palmyra Bowling utilizes users' IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general. This information does not contain anything that can personally identify users. Using email addresses provided at registration or otherwise, Palmyra Bowling periodically sends out promotional email to our users about services and products offerings. Users can indicate that they do or do not wish to receive email information from Palmyra Bowling. Third parties are not authorized to contact our users through the use of our email lists. Upon request, Palmyra Bowling will remove users (and their information) from our database or permit them to "opt-out" of any further email communications or contact. Our site uses cookies to deliver content specific to users' interests and to honor their preferences. This information is used to assist us in creating a site that will serve the needs of our users.

### General

Palmyra Bowling is not responsible for the content or the privacy polices of websites to which it may provide links or the websites of its advertisers or clients. Please review our Terms andConditions for using this Web Site.

### Additional Privacy Protection for Children

This Site is not aimed at children less than 13 years of age. Any Informationsubmitted through the Contact Form and Fun Club pages that we know or reasonably believe originated from a child less than 13 years of age will bedeleted. Children should never reveal their addresses, phone numbers or otherpersonally identifying information to any strangers on the Internet.

Palmyra Bowling uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal informationdisclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to responsiblethird parties after permission from the user.

Individuals or their parents or guardians may request a deletion of userinformation by contacting Palmyra Bowling.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with Palmyra Bowling, please feel free to contact us at the following address:

Palmyra Bowling  
1218 E Main St  
Palmyra, PA 17078
